God is still saying something.
During the live Sunday service on the 19th of February 2017,
Prophet T.B. Joshua prophesied about a natural disaster in Southern Africa.
These were his words
I am seeing some natural disasters like wind - a bad wind coming from the sea.
Bad nature - a natural disaster
that will destroy many things,
that will move from one country to another.
Let us rise and pray
for part of Southern Africa -
moving from countries like: Mozambique, South Africa, Botswana and some areas there.
In Jesus Christ's name, we pray.
A magnitude 6.5 quake struck a remote region of Botswana on Monday,
yet a renowned Kalahari game reserve.
Tremors were also felt in several cities in South Africa as well as Swaziland and Zimbabwe.
According to the United States Geological Survey,
the epicenter of the quake was nearly 250 kilometers Northwest of the capital Gaborone,
at a depth of 12 kilometers. It rumbled throughout the capital for about thirty seconds,
sending shockwaves across the Southern African country.